A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Penitentiary, 1796-1991 (bulk 1906-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Prisoner Records, 1865-1990., Extent: 79.22 cubic feet of records, 128 volumes and 16 reels of microfilm. (Box 9-384, 694-696., Volume 1-127, 270., Microfilm Misc. Reels 5989-6004.)
  - Series II. Subseries B. Photographs and Negatives, 1906-1961, 1965-1966. (Box 19-349, 694-696., Volume 127.)
    - Series II.B.III. Inmate Negatives, 1906-1914 and 1934-1961. (Box 46-349, 696.)
      - II.B.III.4c. Original Negatives (Safety Film) - Not Duplicated (No Prints made) (Box 232-349.)
        - 67470-67769 [67480, 67481, 67486, 67487, 67505, 67584, 67585, 67586, 67600, 67617, 67652, 67653, 67654, 67656, 67676, 67724, 67728, 67758, 67768 missing]. (Box 310)
        - 67770-68049 [67773, 67845, 67846, 67847, 67848, 67849, 67850, 67897, 67911, 67970, 67971, 67972, 68030, 68044 missing]. (Box 311)
        - 68050-68349 [68180, 68181, 68186, 68244, 68261, 68311 missing]. (Box 312)
        - 68350-68649 [68384, 68385, 68390, 68442, 68497, 68498, 68547, 68548, 68593, 68627, 68628, 68640, 68646 missing]. (Box 313)
        - 68650-68949 [68665, 68754, 68807, 68910, 68918, 68937, 68938 missing]. (Box 314)
        - 68950-69249 [68953, 69042, 69088, 69112, 69113, 69128, 69179, 69184, 69185, 69192 missing]. (Box 315)
        - 69250-69549 [69319, 69322, 69323, 69337, 69352, 69364, 69424, 69468, 69469, 69474, 69547 missing]. (Box 316)
        - 69550-69848 [69621, 69622, 69623, 69694, 69697, 69700, 69717, 69727, 69732, 69808, 69849 missing]. (Box 317)
        - 69850-70149 [69966, 69967, 69968, 69981, 69982, 69983, 69984, 70050, 70051, 70052, 70062, 70063, 70069, 70076, 70077, 70113, 70115, 70142 missing]. (Box 318)
        - 70150-70449 [70199, 70200, 70282, 70283, 70284, 70287, 70305, 70311, 70347, 70383, 70384, 70443, 70444 missing]. (Box 319)
        - 70450-70749 [70451, 70492, 70524, 70538, 70539, 70573, 70574, 70618, 70639, 70644, 70665, 70666, 70713, 70714, 70748 missing]. (Box 320)
        - 70750-71049 [70798, 70804, 70836, 70884, 70885, 70900, 70923, 70933, 70935, 70961, 70965, 71006 missing]. (Box 321)
        - 71050-71349 [71078, 71079, 71080, 71081, 71109, 71141, 71196, 71197, 71198, 71253, 71324 missing]. (Box 322)
        - 71350-71649 [71357, 71358, 71359, 71373, 71442, 71443, 71444, 71481, 71517, 71518, 71556, 71557, 71558, 71563, 71564, 71591, 71592 missing]. (Box 323)
        - 71650-71949 [71664, 71665, 71694, 71695, 71787, 71788, 71854, 71866, 71883, 71884, 71885, 71886 missing]. (Box 324)
        - 71950-72249 [71978, 71979, 71982, 72072, 72129, 72158, 72195, 72225, 72242, 72243 missing]. (Box 325)
        - 72250-72549 [72257, 72260, 72277, 72283, 72284, 72333, 72334, 72424, 72425, 72462, 72524 missing]. (Box 326)
        - 72550-72849 [72606, 72641, 72642, 72643, 72646, 72647, 72671, 72750, 72807, 72808 missing]. (Box 327)
        - 72850-73149 [72931, 72965, 72979, 73048, 73061, 73081, 73097, 73125 missing]. (Box 328)
        - 73150-73449 [73161, 73253, 73260, 73326, 73371, 73376, 73405, 73406, 73434 missing]. (Box 329)
        - 73450-73749 [73456, 73468, 73517, 73676, 73691 missing]. (Box 330)
        - 73750-74049 [73765, 73766, 73819, 73856, 73857, 73960, 73994, 73995, 73996, 73997, 74007, 74008 missing]. (Box 331)
        - 74050-74349 [74062, 74063, 74071, 74116, 74117, 74136, 74142, 74192, 74212, 74213, 74230, 74245, 74270, 74272, 74273, 74338, 74339 missing]. (Box 332)
        - 74350-74649 [74377, 74378, 74420, 74468, 74469, 74470, 74590, 74591, 74592, 74593, 74594, 74641, 74647 missing]. (Box 333)
        - 74650-74949 [74688, 74697, 74698, 74752, 74793, 74794, 74806,, 74842, 74872, 74873 missing]. (Box 334)
        - 74950-75249 [74952, 75109, 75135, 75136, 75179, 75180, 75184, 75185 missing]. (Box 335)
        - 75250-75549 [75258, 75279, 75327, 75374, 75406, 75495, 75496, 75506, 75507, 75508, 75509, 75539 missing]. (Box 336)
        - 75550-75849 [75565, 75571, 75577, 75621, 75722, 75723, 75724, 75805, 75806, 75818 missing]. (Box 337)
        - 75850-76149 [75869, 75896, 75936, 75949, 75985, 75986, 76067 missing]. (Box 338)
        - 76150-76446 [76196, 76199, 76250, 76269, 76359, 76360, 76447, 76448, 76449 missing]. (Box 339)
        - 76452-76749 [76450, 76451, 76468. 76469, 76495, 76516, 76531, 76574, 76588, 76637, 76647, 76648, 76709 missing]. (Box 340)
        - 76754-77049 [76750, 76751, 76752, 76753, 76928, 76929, 76930, 76971, 76994 missing]. (Box 341)
        - 77050-77349 [77080, 77122, 77123, 77124, 77134, 77135, 77136, 77163, 77177, 77178, 77179, 77197, 77224, 77250, 77251, 77252, 77332 missing]. (Box 342)
        - 77350-77649 [77359, 77360, 77400, 77410, 77474, 77516, 77553, 77576, 77626, 77627 missing]. (Box 343)
        - 77650-77949 [77684, 77685, 77686, 77850, 77851, 77918, 77919, 77920, 77932, 77933 missing]. (Box 344)
        - 77950-78249 [77995, 77996, 77997, 78111, 78127, 78136, 78198 missing]. (Box 345)
        - 78250-78549 [78271, 78272, 78273, 78286, 78287, 78288, 78289, 78427, 78463, 78464 missing]. (Box 346)
        - 78551-78848 [78550, 78615, 78616, 78620, 78621, 78622, 78651, 78674, 78675, 78679, 78756, 78804, 78805, 78806, 78817, 78843, 78844, 78845, 78849, 78850 missing]. (Box 347)
        - 78851-79149 [78850, 78917, 78941, 78977, 78978, 79034 missing]. (Box 348)
        - 79150-79449, 79648, 79701, 80960-80968 [79160, 79177, 79188, 79215, 79272, 79306, 79307, 79405, 79406 missing]. (Box 349)
  - Series II. Subseries C. Penitentiary Commitment Orders, 1865-1896. (Box 350-365.)
    This subseries is housed in 16 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by prisoner name. These records consist of commitment papers for the years 1865-1896. Not all commitment papers for this time period are extant. This subseries only represents a small fraction of the total number of prisoners committed and released from the penitentiary during this time period. The commitment papers include the name and race of prisoner, court, locality, date of indictment and trial (including the names of the grand jury and jury), crime, date of conviction and sentence. Some documents include notations by penitentiary staff that list date received at penitentiary, prisoner register book and page numbers and date discharged. A small number include pardon documents issued by the Governor. One record of note is a commitment order dated 4 September 1865 for Samuel Van Winkle, Co. G, 5th Pennsylvania Cavalry, who was court-martialed and sentenced to six months in the penitentiary for desertion.
    - Adair, Jefferson - Anderson, William. (Box 350, Folder 1)
    - Armistead, Laura - Ayres, Wesley. (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - Bacon, Albert - Banks, George. (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - Banks, Rebecca - Baylor, Henry. (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - Beal, Boas - Bishop, Nelson. (Box 350, Folder 5)
    - Bissell, Joe - Booth, Jenny. (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - Bosman, E. - Braxton, Carter. (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - Braxton, Charles - Brooks, William. (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Albert - Brown, John Thomas. (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Joshua - Burnes, Daniel. (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - Burrel, Thomas - Byrd, Jr., William. (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - Caldwell, Berry - Canady, Andrew. (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - Carney, Massie - Carter, John. (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Mary - Chapman, Charles. (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - Chapman, Herbert - Church, John W. (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Church, William - Clarke, Edward W. (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - Clarke, James - Coble, C.C. (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - Colbert, M. - Coleman, Richard. (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - Coleman, Robert - Conner, Joseph. (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - Cook, Allen - Corum, Enoch. (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - Cousin, Henry - Crawford, William. (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - Creekmore, John - Curtis, William. (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - Dabney, John F. - Davis, Edward. (Box 353, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Elijah - Dickinson, Levi. (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - Dickinson, Robert Henry - Dorcas, Charles R. (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - Dorsey, George - Edwards, John. (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - Edwards, Thomas - Ewell, Wesley (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - Felon, Herbert - Forbes, William H. (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - Ford, Edward - Furr, David. (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - Gaines, Thomas - Giles, Wesley. (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - Gill, William - Goodman, Thomas A. (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Gordon, Barbara - Grymes, E. Buford. (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - Hackley, William - Harmon, George. (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Eddie - Harris, William H. (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, John - Henderson, John. (Box 355, Folder 6)
    - Henderson, Richard - Hilton, Aron. (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - Hines, Anderson - Horace, McHenry. (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - Howard, Samuel - Hyde, Lacy. (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - I'Anson, Henry - Jackson, Charles. (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Duke - James, Pug. (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - James, Reuben - Jennings, Marshall. (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - Jennings, Polly - Johnson, Frank. (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, George - Johnson, Lafayette. (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Mary - Johnson, William H. (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, William L. - Jones, James. (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Jim - Jones, Ned. (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Nelson - Jordan, Thomas. (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - Joyner, Amos - Kelley, William. (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, James - Kinney, Aaron. (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Kinney, Jackson - Law, John Henry. (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Layne, William - Lewis, Betty. (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - Lewis, Caroline - Lewis, Warren. (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, William - Littleton, Oscar. (Box 358, Folder 6)
    - Littrell, James - Lucas, George. (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Luck, Samuel - Martin, Harvey. (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Martin, Ned - McCrickard, Charles T. (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - McDonald, Charles - Miles, Robert. (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - Miller, George - Mitchell, D.H. (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - Mitchell, Lonzo - Morris, Ben. (Box 359, Folder 6)
    - Morris, Charles - Myers, Peter. (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - Nappier, Thomas - Newman, John. (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - Newsom, Jerry B. - O'Brien, Hannah. (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Oby, Harvey - Owens, George. (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - Page, Abraham - Peterson, Lewis. (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - Peterson, Pendleton - Pollard, Burr. (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - Porter, Amos - Preston, Lizzie E. (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Price, Dock - Ratliff, J.H. (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - Read, Jane - Richeson, William. (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Riddick, Luther - Robinson, Elvira. (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, J.E. - Rowles, Ward. (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - Rowlet, Robert - Scott, Alexander. (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - Scott, David - Scott, Step. (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - Scott, Washington - Smallwood, Stonewall J. (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Alexander - Smith, William. (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - Sneed, Melviria - Stokes, Robert. (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Street, Robert - Taylor, Sandy. (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Trab - Thompson, James M. (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - Thompson, John - Turner, Thomas. (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - Vainwright, Walter - Waddill, J.E. (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - Waddy, Henry - Waller, Richard. (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - Waller, Sam - Washington, General. (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - Washington, George - Washington, Richard. (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - Washington, Samuel - West, Charles. (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - West, Nancy - White, Joseph D. (Box 364, Folder 1)
    - White, Mark - Whittington, John. (Box 364, Folder 2)
    - Wiggins, Albert - Williams, Dennis. (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Henry - Williams, Roberts. (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Samuel - Wilson, Jim. (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, John - Winslow, Abraham. (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - Winston, William - Woodhouse, Henry. (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - Woods, Isaac - Wright, John W. (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Wright, Lewis - Young, N.H. (Box 365, Folder 3)
  - Series II. Subseries D. Inmate Index Cards for Felons, 1914, 1919, 1921-1949. (Box 366-371.)
    This subseries is housed in six (6) boxes and is arranged alphabetically by prisoner name. These records consist of index cards containing prisoner information for the years 1914, 1919 and 1921 to 1949. Not all index cards for this time period are extant. This subseries only represents a small fraction of the total number of prisoners committed to the penitentiary during this time period. Each index card includes the prisoner name, prisoner number, alias, race, fingerprint classification, crime, term, date and place received, date term expires, jail time, criminal history, measurements (hat, shoe, collar, coat, and pants), previous address, names and addresses of immediate family (spouse, parents and siblings) and person to notify in case of an emergency.
    - Boggs, Cowan - Dykes, Ralph (Box 366)
    - Eacho, Jr., Clarence A. - Jones, Everett (Box 367)
    - Jones, F.P. - Myers, Joseph E. (Box 368)
    - Nachimson, Mortimer - Russell, Woodrow (Box 369)
    - St. Clair, Charles - Williams, Junius (Box 370)
    - Williams, K.W. - Zygmont, Leonard (Box 371)
  - Series II. Subseries E. Execution Files, 1908-1970. (Box 372-384.)
    This subseries is housed in thirteen boxes and is arranged numerically by file number. In 1908 the Virginia General Assembly passed legislation stating that all executions would occur at the Penitentiary by means of electrocution. Between October 1908 and March 1962, Virginia executed 236 people. In 1972 the United States Supreme Court ruled the death penalty unconstitutional on grounds that the death penalty was administered too arbitrarily (Furman v. Georgia). The same court in 1976 ruled that Georgia's new law for capital cases removed the administration issues raised in the Furman decision. Virginia resumed executions in 1982. These records documents Virginia's executions between 1908 and 1962. These records include correspondence, court orders and records, lists of witnesses, newspaper clippings, photographs and negatives, prisoner records (including personal data), respites and telegrams. Also included is one box of records (b384) containing files for prisoners not executed (stay of execution, sentenced reversed on appeal). Photographs for the first 60 prisoners executed are located in Series II. Prisoner Records, Subseries B. Photographs and Negatives (b19). Access to this collection is restricted for 50 years from date of execution. Additional execution files from the 1980s and 1990s can be found in Series IV. Office of the Superintendent, Subseries B. Correspondence, Raymond Muncy (b479 and b480). These records are also restricted for 50 years from date of execution.
    - No. 1 - Henry Smith, 13 October 1908. (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - No. 2 - Winston Green, 30 October 1908. (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - No. 3 - Frank Davenport, 4 January 1909. (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - No. 4 - Charles Gillespie, 18 February 1909. (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - No. 5 - Benjamin Gilbert, 19 March 1909. (Box 372, Folder 5)
    - No. 6 - Arthelius Christian, 22 March 1909. (Box 372, Folder 6)
    - No. 7 - James Smith, 8 April 1909. (Box 372, Folder 7)
    - No. 8 - Berry Seaborne, 16 April 1909. (Box 372, Folder 8)
    - No. 9 - John Brown, 30 April 1909. (Box 372, Folder 9)
    - No. 10 - William Brown, 30 April 1909. (Box 372, Folder 10)
    - No. 11 - Joe Taylor, 5 May 1909. (Box 372, Folder 11)
    - No. 12 - Isham Taylor, 5 May 1909. (Box 372, Folder 11)
    - No. 13 - Lewis Jenkins, 7 May 1909. (Box 372, Folder 11)
    - No. 14 - John Fleming, 30 July 1909. (Box 372, Folder 12)
    - No. 15 - William H. Wise, 27 August 1909. (Box 372, Folder 13)
    - No. 16 - Howard H. Bragg, 24 September 1909. (Box 372, Folder 14)
    - No. 17 - Jack Traynham, 12 November 1909. (Box 372, Folder 15)
    - No. 18 - Harry Robinson, 9 December 1909. (Box 372, Folder 16)
    - No. 19 - Clifton Breckinridge, 17 December 1909. (Box 372, Folder 17)
    - No. 20 - Thurman Spinner, 14 January 1910. (Box 372, Folder 18)
    - No. 21 - W.P. Parker, 25 January 1910. (Box 372, Folder 19)
    - No. 22 - William Goins, 28 January 1910. (Box 372, Folder 20)
    - No. 23 - Howard Little, 11 February 1910. (Box 372, Folder 21)
    - No. 24 - Willie Blake, 11 February 1910. (Box 372, Folder 22)
    - No. 25 - Elijah Rouse, 25 April 1910. (Box 372, Folder 23)
    - No. 26 - Henry Smith, 3 June 1910. (Box 372, Folder 24)
    - No. 27 - Thomas Noel, 10 June 1910. (Box 372, Folder 25)
    - No. 28 - Angelo S. Hamilton, 1 July 1910. (Box 372, Folder 26)
    - No. 29 - Arch Brown, 22 September 1910. (Box 372, Folder 27)
    - No. 30 - Pink Barbour, 23 September 1910. (Box 372, Folder 28)
    - No. 31 - John Eccles, 11 November 1910. (Box 372, Folder 29)
    - No. 32 - Waverly Coles, 25 November 19. (Box 372, Folder 30)
    - No. 33 - J.J. Smyth, 16 December 1910. (Box 372, Folder 31)
    - No. 34 - Harry Sitlington, 16 December 1910. (Box 372, Folder 32)
    - No. 35 - Richard H. Biggs, 7 January 1911. (Box 372, Folder 33)
    - No. 36 - Alex Holloman, 2 June 1911. (Box 372, Folder 34)
    - No. 37 - Henry Clay Beattie, 24 November 1911. (Box 372, Folder 35)
    - No. 38 - John Williamson 15 March 1912. (Box 372, Folder 36)
    - No. 39 - John Ferby, 14 June 1912. (Box 372, Folder 37)
    - No. 40 - William Price, 14 June 1912. (Box 372, Folder 38)
    - No. 41 - Clarence Nixon, 21 June 1912. (Box 373, Folder 1)
    - No. 42 - Byrd Jackson, 21 June 1912. (Box 373, Folder 2)
    - No. 43 - Virginia Christian, 16 August 1912. (Box 373, Folder 3)
    - No. 44 - Herbert Peyton, 8 November 1912. (Box 373, Folder 4)
    - No. 45 - Richard T. Quarles, 3 January 1913. (Box 373, Folder 5)
    - No. 46 - Roy M. Sullivan, 28 February 1913. (Box 373, Folder 6)
    - No. 47 - Floyd Allen, 28 March 1913. (Box 373, Folder 7)
    - No. 48 - Claude Allen, 28 March 1913. (Box 373, Folder 8)
    - No. 49 - James Goode, 2 May 1913. (Box 373, Folder 9)
    - No. 50 - Alfred Wright, 16 May 1913. (Box 373, Folder 10)
    - No. 51 - F.L. Hargrove, 26 June 1913. (Box 373, Folder 11)
    - No. 52 - Nelson V. Carter, 27 June 1913. (Box 373, Folder 12)
    - No. 53 - Owen Goggin, 27 June 1913. (Box 373, Folder 13)
    - No. 54 - Benjamin Baily, 8 August 1913. (Box 373, Folder 14)
    - No. 55 - William Glinn, 16 August 1913. (Box 373, Folder 15)
    - No. 56 - Minnie Collins, 31 October 1913. (Box 373, Folder 16)
    - No. 57 - Newell Walker, 5 December 1913. (Box 373, Folder 17)
    - No. 58 - Lee Archer, 5 December 1913. (Box 373, Folder 18)
    - No. 59 - Charlton Moore, 16 January 1914. (Box 373, Folder 19)
    - No. 60 - Willie Rhodes, 30 January 1914. (Box 373, Folder 20)
    - No. 61 - Marion Lee, 19 March 1914. (Box 373, Folder 21)
    - No. 62 - Walter Boyd, 27 March 1914. (Box 373, Folder 22)
    - No. 63 - George Woods, 22 May 1914. (Box 373, Folder 23)
    - No. 64 - Will Calloway, 10 July 1914. (Box 373, Folder 24)
    - No. 65 - Willie Puryear, 7 August 1914. (Box 373, Folder 25)
    - No. 66 - Henry Coach, 21 August 1914. (Box 373, Folder 26)
    - No. 67 - John Edmunds, 18 December 1914. (Box 373, Folder 27)
    - No. 68 - Arthur Neale, 8 January 1915. (Box 373, Folder 28)
    - No. 69 - Charles Miller, 26 March 1915. (Box 373, Folder 29)
    - No. 70 - Herbert Caple, 30 April 1915. (Box 373, Folder 30)
    - No. 71 - Skipwith Sydner, 21 May 1915. (Box 373, Folder 31)
    - No. 72 - Thomas Cole, 4 June 1915. (Box 373, Folder 32)
    - No. 73 - Lem Jones, 16 June 1915. (Box 373, Folder 33)
    - No. 74 - Luther Canter, 11 June 1915. (Box 373, Folder 34)
    - No. 75 - John Lewis Rollins, 20 August 1915. (Box 373, Folder 35)
    - No. 76 - George Matthews, 20 August 1915. (Box 373, Folder 36)
    - No. 77 - Ed Pryor, 10 September 1915. (Box 373, Folder 37)
    - No. 78 - Sherman Stanfield, 17 September 1915. (Box 373, Folder 38)
    - No. 79 - Percy Ellis, 15 March 1916. (Box 373, Folder 39)
    - No. 80 - Joe Lee, 21 April 1916. (Box 373, Folder 40)
    - No. 81 - John Henry William, 28 May 1916. (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - No. 82 - Milton Maloy, 7 July 1916. (Box 374, Folder 2)
    - No. 83 - Richard Green, 25 August 1916. (Box 374, Folder 3)
    - No. 84 - Clifford Mickens, 25 August 1916. (Box 374, Folder 4)
    - No. 85 - Henry Lewis, 8 September. (Box 374, Folder 5)
    - No. 86 - Minser Harris, 2 October 1916. (Box 374, Folder 6)
    - No. 87 - James Corbett, 2 October 1916. (Box 374, Folder 7)
    - No. 88 - Hansom Warren, 16 June 1917. (Box 374, Folder 8)
    - No. 89 - Hamilton Cosby, 20 June 1917. (Box 374, Folder 9)
    - No. 90 - Robert Jones, 20 June 1917. (Box 374, Folder 10)
    - No. 91 - Albert Barrett, 31 August 1917. (Box 374, Folder 11)
    - No. 92 - William Burgess, 26 October 1917. (Box 374, Folder 12)
    - No. 93 - Paul Langhorne, 7 June 1918. (Box 374, Folder 13)
    - No. 94 - Guy Nixon, 2 July 1918. (Box 374, Folder 14)
    - No. 95 - Tolson Bailey, 2 July 1918. (Box 374, Folder 15)
    - No. 96 - Harvey Stuart, 26 March 1919. (Box 374, Folder 16)
    - No. 97 - Horace Williams, 26 March 1919. (Box 374, Folder 17)
    - No. 98 - Jerry Warren, 27 June 1919. (Box 374, Folder 18)
    - No. 99 - Emper Jones, 30 October 1919. (Box 374, Folder 19)
    - No. 100 - Robert Williams, 13 November 1920. (Box 374, Folder 20)
    - No. 101 - John H. Williams, 5 March 1921. (Box 374, Folder 21)
    - No. 102 - Giles Sydnor, 8 April 1921. (Box 374, Folder 22)
    - No. 103 - Raleigh Haskins, 30 September 1921. (Box 374, Folder 23)
    - No. 104 - Judge Griffin, 30 September 1921. (Box 374, Folder 23)
    - No. 105 - Wilmer Amos Hadley, 9 December 1921. (Box 374, Folder 24)
    - No. 106 - Harry Hart, 23 January 1922. (Box 374, Folder 25)
    - No. 107 - Edmond Thompson, 7 February 1922. (Box 374, Folder 26)
    - No. 108 - Henry Lockett, 23 February 1922. (Box 374, Folder 27)
    - No. 109 - Thomas Sparks, 24 February 1922. (Box 374, Folder 28)
    - No. 110 - Will Elmoe, 31 March 1922. (Box 374, Folder 29)
    - No. 111 - Henry Barnes, 4 April 1922. (Box 374, Folder 30)
    - No. 112 - Ernest Brown, 26 May 1922. (Box 374, Folder 31)
    - No. 113 - Willie E. Clayton, 5 January 1923. (Box 374, Folder 32)
    - No. 114 - Alvin W. Harris, 6 February 1923. (Box 374, Folder 33)
    - No. 115 - George Wriggins, 2 March 1923. (Box 374, Folder 34)
    - No. 116 - Sam Riddick, 18 June 1923. (Box 374, Folder 35)
    - No. 117 - Robert Corbett, 28 September 1923. (Box 374, Folder 36)
    - No. 118 - Fritz Lewis, 12 September 1924. (Box 374, Folder 37)
    - No. 119 - Otto Clear, 12 September 1924. (Box 374, Folder 37)
    - No. 120 - Isaac A. Cooper, 6 March 1925. (Box 374, Folder 38)
    - No. 121 - Prince Dandridge, 12 March 1925. (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - No. 122 - Jesse Carter, 17 April 1925. (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - No. 123 - Percy Lee, 1 May 1925. (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - No. 124 - Rodney Hoke, 10 July 1925. (Box 375, Folder 4)
    - No. 125 - Horace Allen, 17 July 1925. (Box 375, Folder 5)
    - No. 126 - Henry Perman, 29 September 1925. (Box 375, Folder 6)
    - No. 127 - Doc Earl McMillan, 9 October 1925. (Box 375, Folder 7)
    - No. 128 - William Spencer, 22 January 1926. (Box 375, Folder 8)
    - No. 129 - Rudolph E. Disse, 19 February 1926. (Box 375, Folder 9)
    - No. 130 - Louis Watkins, 19 March 1926. (Box 375, Folder 10)
    - No. 131 - James Patterson, 27 August 1926. (Box 375, Folder 11)
    - No. 132 - James Satchell, 24 September 1926. (Box 375, Folder 12)
    - No. 133 - William Gee, 14 January 1927. (Box 375, Folder 13)
    - No. 134 - Henry Perfey, 15 April 1927. (Box 375, Folder 14)
    - No. 135 - William Thomas, 15 April 1927. (Box 375, Folder 15)
    - No. 136 - Louis F. Boersig, 7 July 1927. (Box 375, Folder 16)
    - No. 137 - William Nelson, 15 November 1927. (Box 375, Folder 17)
    - No. 138 - Shirley Winningham, 25 January 1928. (Box 375, Folder 18)